Privacy Policy
==============

**5PLAY.ORG Privacy Policy**

_5PLAY.ORG_ is committed to protecting consumer privacy online. We believe that greater protection of personal privacy on the Web will not only protect our users, but also increase users confidence and ultimately their participation in online activities. The purpose of our policy is to inform you about the types of information we gather about you when you visit our site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of the information. _5PLAY.ORG_ strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. By using our site, you consent to our website’s privacy policy and Terms of use.

**How We Gather Information and Technologies We Use?**

This section provides information about the information we collect and how the technologies we utilize work.

**Cookies.**

We use "cookies." The cookies we place on your computer are very small text files that uniquely identify your browser and may be sent to your computer or mobile device. They are stored on your hard drive and communicate with our servers only when you are visiting our websites. We use cookies to improve the quality of _5PLAY.ORG_. They allow us to monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and number of pages viewed. They also allow us to optimize _5PLAY.ORG_ to make sure that we are delivering the best possible experience to our users. Your web browser is likely already set to accept cookies, yet you may choose to block cookies in your web browser’s settings. Note that blocking cookies may result in some features not being able to function properly. To learn more about controlling browser cookies visit: [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=1).

Additionally, we allow third parties that display advertisements, search listings, and other content on portions of _5PLAY.ORG_ to set and access their cookies on your computer or device and any cookies are subject to the applicable third parties privacy policies and not ours.

**Device Information.**

We collect information regarding the Internet browser, computer, tablet, mobile phone, smartphone or other device utilized to access _5PLAY.ORG_ to ensure that _5PLAY.ORG_ is optimized for those devices.

**Analytics.**

We use third party information, reports and analysis about the usage and browsing patterns of users of _5PLAY.ORG_. The Analytics we use do not identify individual users of _5PLAY.ORG_.

**Log Files.**

We may also automatically log certain anonymous information about visitors to _5PLAY.ORG_.

**Use of Third Party Ad Networks and Social Networks**

_5PLAY.ORG_ expects its partners, advertisers to respect the privacy of our users. However, third parties, including our partners, advertisers and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices.

**Changes in Privacy Policy**

_5PLAY.ORG_ reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a notice at the Site explaining that we are changing our Privacy Policy.

**Contacting the Site**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us [\[email protected\]](https://5play.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).
